I'm sorry, I forgot to turn off the sound.
Okay, let's do it again today.
Can you hear my voice?
I'm your lovely MoYi, I'm back again.
Because I've been going back to the studio for more than a month,
I'm a little too nervous today, so I forgot to turn off the background music.
I'm sorry.
How about today?
Let's learn about our other talents.
Last time, our Ivy teacher talked about hair loss.
I don't know if you've listened to it seriously.
Now let's learn about other talents.
Click on Fabric 1 at the top of the object window.
You can see a type of hair loss here.
This is a default type of hair loss.
It's a normal hair loss type.
Click on the triangle at the bottom.
You can see that there are many other types of hair loss.
We can choose our own hair loss type according to our own needs.
It's more realistic.
There are a total of 12 types of hair loss.
There are some types of hair loss with the word REND ONLY at the back.
This type of hair loss can only be shown when the hair loss is only shown.
There are a total of five types of hair loss.
If you want to know how to get rid of hair loss from hair loss,
let's go to the website.
We are at the website at the top of the top of the page.
If you have any ideas about hair loss,
see our live streaming.
Today we are going to learn about other hair loss types.
I'm sorry.
I was the one who showed you my hair loss tips.
I'm going to show you my hair loss tips.
This time I will show you my hair loss tips.
I've taught you how to get rid of your hair loss tips.
Sorry, I'm still a little nervous.
Now let's take a look at how these materials are applied.
Let's see what each material represents.
The first material is matte.
It represents the reflection of a normal plant.
The second material is shiny.
It represents the reflection of a shiny plant.
The third material is silk.
It represents the glow of silk.
All the silk materials can be used to represent it.
The fourth material represents the reflection of a silk plant.
The fifth material represents the expression of a needlework.
If you need it, you can watch our last live stream.
The next material represents the diamond effect.
The glass material represents glass.
The next material represents the glitter effect.
The next material represents the light effect.
The last material represents leather.
The next material represents plastic.
I'm sorry, I'm the one who is talking about the
I.V.
I'm sorry, I'm the one who is talking about the I.V.
Let's go back to our closet and see how we are going to use these materials.
You can see there's a skirt here.
As you can see, there is a skirt here.
I want to give this skirt a silk texture.
Sorry, I'm so nervous.
At the window of the drawing room,
you can see the fabric inside the fabric storage.
Click on it.
Here is the silk fabric that we have provided.
We can apply the silk fabric on this large piece of fabric.
You can drag it directly into 3D clothing.
You can see the silk texture.
In addition to this,
we can directly click on the fabric we have provided,
and give it a silk texture on the attribute type.
Now,
you can see the silk texture.
You may not see it clearly now.
Let's give it a blue color.
Now, you can see a silk-like skirt in my 3D window.
Next,
you can see the strength of the front color
and the strength of the side color.
The strength of the front color
refers to the combination of the front color.
When the straight color
is larger,
the more it is saturated,
the more blue color will appear on the clothing.
Now, I adjust the number here to 2.
You can see that there is a lot of blue color on my clothes.
Right?
When the straight color is smaller,
the more the blue color is saturated,
the more it is close to the silk texture.
Here,
we only need to give it a suitable straight color.
Then,
it is done.
The color on the side is the color of the edge.
The smaller the straight color,
the less the reflection on the edge.
When you open the 3D window,
you will see the clothes,
and there is no sense of light on the edge.
However,
in terms of silk,
we certainly hope that the reflection on the edge
will be higher,
right?
We will make its finger higher
to make it closer to the silk texture.
It will be more similar to the glow effect of a silk dragon.
And then at the bottom, we can see that there is a surface roughness and a reflection intensity.
The lower the surface roughness, the smoother this costume will be.
You can take a look at it.
I'm going to adjust it to zero now.
It's a very smooth surface.
But for the silk dragon, we need to adjust the roughness of the surface to the maximum.
Because the surface is still very rough.
And its reflection intensity refers to its ability to reflect light.
The higher its intensity, the more it can reflect light.
You can take a look at it.
Now I'm on the white dragon.
Its reflection effect is very good.
But the effect of the silk dragon is relatively weak.
So we need to adjust the reflection intensity to zero.
You can take a look at it.
I'm going to adjust the reflection intensity to zero.
And then you can see a very smooth surface in the 3D screen.
Now you can see that there is a belt here.
I want to make the belt look like metal.
You can find this fabric in the 3D window.
And then you can analyze the material in the material editor.
Now you can see that it has a metallic feel to it, and it's a silver color.
Let's change the color to yellow to give it a golden feel.
It looks more luxurious.
Now you can see that it has a golden effect.
You can see different reflections in the rotation.
You can see that it only has the surface roughness and no reflection.
That's because metal has a better reflection.
If we reduce the reflection, the light will be different from the real metal.
So we can cancel the reflection here.
Now you can adjust the surface roughness to see if it's smooth or not.
Now you can see the metal belt in the 3D window.
Now let's take a look at the chest.
The chest is an obj-type component.
Let's take a look at the 3D window.
Let's take a look at the chest.
We'll give it a glass material.
You can see that there's a symbol behind the glass material.
It's a static reflection.
So it can only be turned on when it's in a state of reflection.
So let's turn on a reflection.
Let's turn on the synchronization reflection.
Oh, it's a little slow now.
Maybe everyone needs to wait a little bit.
Now we can see the chest in the 3D window.
It's made of transparent glass.
There are also surface roughness and reflection intensity.
You can adjust these two values to achieve the effect you want.
The surface of the glass material is relatively smooth,
so you need to reduce the roughness of the surface,
and then increase the reflection intensity,
so its reflection effect is still better.
And then you can see an absorption value at the bottom.
This value represents its transparency.
The smaller the value, the more transparent the glass is.
You may need to wait for a while.
Let's set it to 0.1.
You can see its effect in the mirror window.
You can see the blue color of the bottom of the glass through the glass.
Look at the mirror.
Let's wait for a while.
The bigger the value, the more transparent the glass is.
You can see I set the value to 10.
Now we can't see the blue color of the bottom of the glass through the glass.
But the surface is still reflective.
So you can set the glass to be transparent or not transparent as you want.
Now you can see the blue color.
And here, I need a transparent glass.
So I set the value to 0.1.
You can see the effect of the mirroring effect.
Now let's stop the mirroring and go back to the 2D window.
You can see that there is no glass effect in the 2D window.
Why is it red?
I chose a slightly transparent pink color for the material.
As you can see, it's a pink color.
In addition to adding more material, we can also add a type of button.
Click on the button.
Click on the attribute at the bottom to add a silk color.
I chose this type of button because I want to make the button look like a pearl.
We can adjust the surface roughness at the bottom.
The lower the surface roughness, the smoother the surface.
The higher the reflection intensity, the more reflective it is.
You can adjust the surface roughness according to your needs.
As you can see in the 3D effect, the button looks like a pearl.
We also have the front chest.
Add a normal surface roughness to the front chest.
Add a black color to the front chest.
Add a transparent effect to the front chest.
We can also adjust the color of the thread.
Let's adjust the thread.
Click on the attribute at the bottom.
We can see that the type we choose is a SuMiao.
We will give it a darker gray color.
The transparency is set to 10.
Now you can see the effect of a little bit like a hot glue.
Now you can see the effect like this.
Then we can open our rendering,
and check out the overall effect.
You can see in the window of the rendering,
the light of the silk will be more obvious,
and the metallic reflection.
The little white ball is a button.
You can see that the light of the silk will be more visible.
Since the rendering takes a lot of time,
let's stop the rendering for now.
I have already rendered some pictures,
and I can open them up for you to see.
You can see the overall effect.
The light of the silk will be more visible.
This is how it looks like
when you zoom in.
You can see the transparency of the glass,
including the pearls and the hot glue.
The effect will be more obvious.
Now let's move on to the next one.
Here we can see a dress on a table.
If you are old-fashioned,
you might have an impression of this dress.
Now I want to add some glitter to this dress.
First, find the fabric of the dress,
and change the color of the glitter
in the editor.
The glitter will look more natural later.
Now let's change the shape of the dress.
I'm going to add some glitter to this dress.
There will be a person behind me,
and he can only be seen
through the window of the mirror.
Now let's open the window of the mirror
and turn on the synchronization mirror.
You can see a little bit of the glitter
in the window of the mirror.
This is the glitter.
Now it takes a little bit of time.
Please wait patiently.
You can see the glitter here.
Now let's change the color of the glitter.
I'm going to change the color of the glitter
to a color that is a little bit lighter.
Now you can see the effect of the glitter
in the window of the mirror.
There will be a number below
and a color change.
These two numbers.
And the number of colors
refers to the number of our glitter particles.
When the number of our particles increases,
the more glitter particles we have.
We can see the glitter particles
in the window of the mirror.
Now it is 300.
It is much more than 100.
Now we can adjust its number to 30.
We can see the effect of the glitter
in the window of the mirror again.
The glitter particles it contains
will be much less.
The overall dress
is not as bright as it used to be.
Now we only need to enter a normal value.
Here I enter 100 million.
There will be a color change below.
Here I show you a picture.
Then you will understand
how to apply it.
The new change is
to randomize the color of the glitter particles.
When the value is 0,
the color will not be random.
Only the set color.
When the value is 1,
the color of the particles
will appear a lot of random colors.
You can see the two pictures below.
The first picture,
its RGB value
is relatively different.
And the first one,
the value of red,
is 255,
which is the largest.
The value of G and B below,
the value of G and B is very similar.
The two values are 3 and 15.
Now we can see
that the whole color here
is only close to the value of red.
It is red.
What we see is basically only red.
The second picture,
its RGB value
is relatively close.
Then we can see
a lot of different colors
in this picture.
So if you want to see
more colors,
the RGB values
need to be adjusted
a little closer.
Let's show you that here.
Let me restart.
Let me go back and look at this.
We are now showing 0.
Let's look at the RGB value here.
This value is relatively close.
Now let's directly
adjust its color.
To 1.
Let's see how it works.
As you can see, there are a lot of colors on the shirt.
Let's wait a bit.
There are a lot of colors on the shirt.
There are red, blue, red, and green.
Let's stop the rendering.
Let's change the color of the shirt.
Let's adjust the RGB value to the maximum.
Let's adjust the blue value to the maximum.
The other values are all 0.
Let's confirm.
Let's open the synchronization rendering.
As you can see,
in the rendering window,
you can see that only the blue color mark will appear.
You can see that only the blue color mark will appear.
There were no other colors left on the shirt.
So if you want the colors to appear randomly,
you must adjust the RGB value
to theработen persona
to theuko color
to the personalized color.
There are many more colors to appear in that哈哈.
I will adjust the color to match the original color
Now you can see there are two shoulder straps
For these two bags, we want to give it a silk texture.
We find the material of these two bags, and then give it a silk type.
You can see the gloss of this silk now.
Now it's white, and you may not see it very clearly.
Now let's change the color.
After changing the color, you may see the gloss of this silk more clearly.
You can also adjust the surface density and the strength of the reflection.
The density of the silk is relatively small, and the strength of the reflection is relatively low.
You can adjust these two values to get the feeling you want.
I'm going to adjust it again here.
I'm going to adjust the surface density and the strength of the reflection again.
Now let's look at the others.
I'm going to adjust the surface density again here.
There is a hole for the
Let's open up the renderer and see if it's a bit slow.
Please wait for a moment.
Now we can see the effect of the renderer in the render window.
Now we can adjust the opacity and contrast.
There are two values in the renderer.
The first one is absorption value.
And the second one is depth value.
The first one is the absorption value.
You can adjust the opacity by adjusting the value.
And the second one is the depth value.
When the value is low, the object will be more transparent.
You can see the transparent effect in the render window.
When the value is higher, the object is not transparent.
When the value is lower, the object is not transparent.
You can see the effect in the render window.
This is the normal value.
This value is related to the thickness of the object.
The thicker the object, the lower the absorption value.
The thicker the effect, the more transparent the image becomes.
And when the value is higher, the object is not transparent.
This is the normal value.
The second one is the opacity value.
The third one is the contrast value.
This value is related to the depth value.
The fourth one is the contrast value.
The fifth one is the opacity value.
Thank you.
Now let's take a look at the effect after rendering
This is the overall effect
This is the detail picture, the detail picture of the bag
Then include this lamp
And this pendant
Okay, that's it for today's live stream
If you have any questions, you can ask in the comments
I saw someone asked how to make a bag
You can search this bag on our Bilibili or on our WeChat official account
There will be a tutorial
You can find all the materials in this class
No, you can't
Do you have any questions?
Someone asked me not to use green all the time
Isn't green pretty?
Why don't you like green?
The pendant is so pretty
Yes, I also think this pendant is really pretty
I don't like the sunlight, so I won't give it to you
Yes, I won't give it to you
I'm worried about you
Does anyone have any questions?
Can you give me the shakira?
No, I can't, you can't have a shakira without me
I will add some more water
I saw someone asked
what is the light for
How to make a lightstick?
We are going to make a lightstick with a piece of paper
Can you believe it?
You can bend the lightstick like this
This is how to make a sculpture
This will tell us if you are willing to make a lightstick
Let's see if anyone is willing to make a lightstick
I haven't eaten yet, so I'm going to do a live stream
It's like I'm eating
Thank you, I haven't done a live stream for over a month
I'm still very nervous
What about other questions about this kind of making a lightstick?
I am thinking how to make a lightstick with this
How about making a lampshade with this
Can you not ask me if I have something to do with this lesson?
I'm late for lunch
Aren't you going to the class?
Are you not going to pay for this course?
Do you want to see the payment?
Your wish, let's pay next time
Your wish is also amazing
It can't be free
Let me show you
The lamp is made of this plate
If the lamp is not made of this plate, I will be angry
Do you want to see the payment?
You can tell us what you want to see in the comments
We will sort it out later
When can the payment be arranged for the course?
Let's see which teacher is available
Can the lamp shine?
Didn't you see it just now? The lamp can shine!
Can the lamp shine? Didn't you see it just now? The lamp can shine!
Of course, it needs to be made of Scher's material
That's how the lamp can shine
The lamp can shine
I won't talk about it.
What can I do about it?
You can actually use a fixed needle to make the shape.
This is actually a plate.
Can you see it?
It's actually a plate.
How to bend it?
Do you want me to have a bowl of lanterns on the scene?
This is too much.
I don't want it.
I just don't want to show my face.
Do you want me to ask you about the content of this class?
Don't be so...
Look at this bag, okay?
Oh, this bag is also quite difficult.
If you ask me about lanterns again,
I'll tell you that the streamer is going to go offline.
I'm going to kill myself.
She handle me with a flash after I was finished.
How to make hot golden逆料
You can put the hot gold on your syrup.
can
Make a
I'm going to use a sticker to stick it on
After that, you can give it another color
For example, gold
You can give it a shiny color
Or give it a shiny color
You can also use a metal sticker
You can try it yourself
Just like this one
You can try it on
You can give it another color
For example, a metal sticker
You can try it on
You can give it another color
Or give it a shiny color
My computer is angry now
Let's take a look at the material of this class, you can ask me about the material of this class.
What do you use for the pattern?
The pattern here can also be done with shining or silk.
It can also be done with plastic.
Which lamp do you use?
Do you mean my light bulb?
I admit that my light bulb is an object.
It is a secondary object.
Why is this?
Why is this always...
Why is this always bothering my lamp?
It is a secondary object.
If we want to change the pattern,
we can only change the appearance of the lamp.
We can only change the appearance of the lamp.
If we want to change the physical attribute,
we can only change the appearance of the lamp.
If we want to change the appearance of the lamp,
Do you have any other questions?
The waist belt made of metal
The thickness of the belt is just to increase the thickness
I didn't ask you about the details before
That's because you guys are always struggling with my light
I said that my light is an OBJ
You can go to other 3D software and make it and pour it in
I said that my light is an OBJ and you can go to other 3D software and make it and pour it in
I said that my light is an OBJ and you can go to other 3D software and make it
honey
All the lighting or lamps used is made of choice
Just make it and turn on theENTER
You can exercise it
Just grab it
You canθ fünf
Do you have any other questions about this lesson?
This lesson is not about how to make a light bulb, okay?
Dear everyone,
I'm so angry that I'm about to burst into tears.
Let's talk about how to make a light bulb.
You can refer to our previous lessons about how to make a light bulb.
There is a lecture about how to make a light bulb.
You can take a look at it.
You can see that there are different types of light bulbs in Bilibili.
One of them is how to make a light bulb.
The main topic is how to make a light bulb.
How to make a light bulb is about how to make a light bulb.
Do you have any other questions?
If you don't have any questions,
we'll end at 9 o'clock.
I hope you won't ask me any more questions about my light bulb.
The effect of lighting a light bulb.
You can do the lighting by lighting the bulb.
Where is the car signal effect?
Sorry, I didn't see your question.
The question about the biggest flash is about the size of the flash.
For the size of the flash, we can't set it up for now.
We can only set it up for now.
What can we do with the flash?
There should be a tutorial about it on our official website.
You can search it on our official website.
The website is www.close3d.com.
Or you can go to the official website from our handbook.
That's it.
What about the car signal effect?
What if the question is about the flash?
There is a 3D effect below the flash.
You can turn on the 3D effect.
The 3D effect will increase the pressure and the fold.
And you will see the effect on the sujet.
You can also turn on the motion adverse effect.
If you cannot get the 3D effect.
Please turn on the 3D effect.
And you will see the effect up close.
Let me show you how it looks like in my eyes.
还有7分钟,我们的直播就要结束了。
在我们的7月31号和8月14号会有两场直播。
大家可以去看一下。
一个是关于模特设置,还有一个是关于模块化设置。
如果对模特的一些广听动作或者是什么之类感兴趣的话,
就可以去看一下我们7月31号的直播。
。
好的,我们就开始。
August 14th is the live stream for the blockchain.
It's a live stream of two handsome guys.
You guys can go and have a look.
Let's give our handsome guys a round of applause.
Do you have any other questions?
The separation of the first part is not clear.
You mean that the separation line is not very obvious, right?
If it's not obvious,
you can enlarge it here.
The separation line is not clear.
I'm curious about my daily life.
Is the content of the live stream normal?
Do you have any other questions?
The live stream is over.
Miss Moly is going to say goodbye to you.
Do you have any other questions?
Miss Moly didn't give you the information you promised to give.
Which time did you not get the information you promised to give?
The live stream ended just now.
You can come to the next live stream earlier.
It's on July 31st and August 14th.
Yezhu999,
which time did you not get the information for the live stream?
Thank you, Miss Moly.
You're welcome.
I will keep heal your wounds.
You are welcome.
Thank you, Miss Moly.
Are there any questions?
All the content of our previous live stream
can be found at
thunderstorm relaxation.ly
You can use the link in the description box to get all the materials.
And all the materials of our master car are not for public sharing.
Please forgive us.
Is there any problem?
If there is no problem, we will be done soon.
So which material you can't find in the page?
He is saying goodbye to me so soon.
No, thank you.
Okay, bye.
We will be done in 1 minute 17 seconds.
All the contents of our live streaming will be broadcasted after 7 days.
So if you have the conditions,
you can watch our live streaming.
If you have any questions,
you can ask them in our official website.
You can scan the WeChat official account in the bottom left corner of our live streaming.
You can send us the contents you want to see.
You can also send us your works.
I will make another announcement and we will be done.
We will have two live streaming on July 31st and August 14th.
One is about model setting.
The other is about model setting.
If you are interested, you can watch it.
The next two live streaming will be about two handsome guys.
You can watch the live streaming for our handsome guys.
See you all in Jianghu.
Bye bye.
Have a nice weekend.
See you.